angrytorro.com 2015-06-22

# Angry Torro - Fun fun fun !

###  Privacy Policy

**We take your privacy very seriously.**

  * ###  Introduction

This privacy policy, which we adapted from a policy originally provided by [Automattic](http://www.automattic.com/), describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use our websites. Please read this notice very carefully.

  * ###  Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Angry Torro collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Angry Torro’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Angry Torro’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Angry Torro may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Angry Torro also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Angry Torro does not use such information to identify its visitors, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

  * ###  Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Angry Torro website choose to interact with Angry Torro in ways that require Angry Torro to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Angry Torro gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for Angry Torro using facebook account to provide a email address. In each case, Angry Torro collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Angry Torro does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

  * ###  Cookies and Web Beacons

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Angry Torro uses cookies to help Angry Torro identify and track visitors, their usage of Angry Torro website, and their website access preferences. Angry Torro visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Angry Torro’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Angry Torro’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

We do use cookies to store information, such as your session information, personal preferences when you visit our site. We also use third party advertisements on Angry Torro website to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). See the Google Privacy Policy at <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html> for more information about data that may be collected, and what it might be used for. More information about using cookies: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site, Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet, Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

  * ###  Links to Third Party Sites

This privacy policy only applies to information collected by Angry Torro. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Angry Torro does not own or control, or employees that Angry Torro does not manage. A Angry Torro website may contain links to third party websites. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if any. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and Angry Torro and its affiliates shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

  * ###  Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Angry Torro may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in Angry Torro’s sole discretion. Angry Torro encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
